nzbclub.com 2016-11-19

# NZBClub.com - Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at error@nzbclub.com. At NZBClub.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by NZBClub.com and how it is used. 

### Log Files

Like most standard Web site servers, NZBClub.com use log files. This includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, browser type, internet service provider ( ISP ), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

### Cookies and Web Beacons

NZBClub.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends. Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. 

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on NZBClub.com. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see. NZBClub.com has no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to opt-out of certain practices. NZBClub.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

#### [**300 GB+ Usenet Trial**](http://www.usenetbest.com/external.aspx?providerid=3)

300 GB+ Free Usenet with no string attached, cancel any time. Free Usenet Software with free search engine. 

#### [Newshosting Unlimited](http://www.usenetbest.com/external.aspx?providerid=21)

**$9.99 monthly or $99.99 annually**   
Unlimited and really fast download speed. Comes with free Usenet Software with search engine. Paypal accepted. Free Fast VPN great for video content like Hulu Plus from desktop, android, and iOS for yearly subscription. [Limited time offer!](http://www.usenetbest.com/external.aspx?providerid=21)

#### [Usenetserver Unlimited](http://www.usenetbest.com/external.aspx?providerid=2)

**$95.4 annually or $10 monthly**

Fast and unlimited Usenet access. 2472+ days retention and comes with free Usenet search engine and free VPN software for annually subscriber. Paypal accepted.

#### [Eweka Special](http://www.usenetbest.com/external.aspx?providerid=16)

Unlimited Usenet Pay What You Need no monthly contract with € Payment Options (Paypal, iDeal, giroPay, paysafecard, ukash, SMS, Bank Transfer)
